<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Beneath the Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://aminmasoudi.github.io</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Beneath the Abstraction</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Welcome to Layer 0</title>
    <link>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/</link>
    <guid>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/</guid>
    <description>Hi, I’m Amin — a backend developer and computer science student who enjoys building clean systems, solving complex problems, and working close to the metal ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 15:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Understanding Networks: A Foundation</title>
    <link>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/blog/Understanding-Networks:-A-Foundation</link>
    <guid>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/blog/Understanding-Networks:-A-Foundation</guid>
    <description>Understanding Networks: A Foundation Networks are an integral part of modern life. Whether you’re using your phone to control smart home devices or liking a friend’s post on Instagram, you’re interacting with networks.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 15:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>mp4 to mp3 Converter - A Micro-Services Example</title>
    <link>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/Projects/msd</link>
    <guid>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/Projects/msd</guid>
    <description>github: micro-serv-des Welcome to the mp4 to mp3 converter, an example project showcasing micro-service system design concepts. What is Micro-Service Design? Micro-service design is an architectural style that structures an application as a collection of small, independent services.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 15:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>SNA</title>
    <link>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/Projects/SNA</link>
    <guid>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/Projects/SNA</guid>
    <description>Graph-Based Social Network Analysis Project: A Graph-Based Social Network Analysis Tool Objective: The task is to design and implement a program that analyzes a social network ...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 15:10:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Api Gateway</title>
    <link>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/Projects/Api-Gateway</link>
    <guid>https://aminmasoudi.github.io/Projects/Api-Gateway</guid>
    <description>Overview This project is an API Gateway built using Starlette and HTTPX. It is currently in the MVP stage, focusing on basic routing functionalities. About API gateway check out RedHat docs to understand the usage.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 15:10:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>